{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sunny",
      "back": "Güneşli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Clear",
      "back": "Açık hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Partly cloudy",
      "back": "Parçalı bulutlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cloudy",
      "back": "Bulutlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Overcast",
      "back": "Kapalı hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Foggy",
      "back": "Sisli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Misty",
      "back": "Puslu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rainy",
      "back": "Yağmurlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Light rain",
      "back": "Hafif yağmur"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Heavy rain",
      "back": "Şiddetli yağmur"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Drizzle",
      "back": "Çiseleme"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Showers",
      "back": "Sağanak yağmur"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Thunderstorm",
      "back": "Gök gürültülü fırtına"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Thunder",
      "back": "Gök gürültüsü"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lightning",
      "back": "Şimşek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Snowy",
      "back": "Karlı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Light snow",
      "back": "Hafif kar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Heavy snow",
      "back": "Yoğun kar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Blizzard",
      "back": "Tipi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sleet",
      "back": "Sulu kar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hail",
      "back": "Dolu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Windy",
      "back": "Rüzgarlı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Light breeze",
      "back": "Hafif meltem"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Strong wind",
      "back": "Kuvvetli rüzgar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Gusty",
      "back": "Ani rüzgar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Stormy",
      "back": "Fırtınalı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hurricane",
      "back": "Kasırga"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tornado",
      "back": "Hortum"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hot",
      "back": "Sıcak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Warm",
      "back": "Ilık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mild",
      "back": "Yumuşak hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cool",
      "back": "Serin"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cold",
      "back": "Soğuk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Freezing",
      "back": "Dondurucu soğuk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Frosty",
      "back": "Ayazlı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Humid",
      "back": "Nemli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Damp",
      "back": "Rutubetli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dry",
      "back": "Kuru"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dusty",
      "back": "Tozlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hazy",
      "back": "Sisli/puslu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Smoggy",
      "back": "Dumanlı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chilly",
      "back": "Serin/üşütücü"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Icy",
      "back": "Buzlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rainbow",
      "back": "Gökkuşağı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Changing",
      "back": "Değişken hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Unstable",
      "back": "Kararsız hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Calm",
      "back": "Sakin hava"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Gloomy",
      "back": "Kasvetli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bright",
      "back": "Parlak"
    }
  ]
}
